The revolution wasn't televised in the 60s.
Is it going to be televised in the 90s?
Well, you know, the catchphrase, what that was all about,
the revolution will not be televised,
that was about the fact that the first change that takes places in your mind.
You have to change your mind before you change the way you live and the way you move.
The revolution is happening here first.
We were saying that the thing that's going to change people
is something that no one will ever be able to capture on film.
It'll just be something that you see and all of a sudden you realize I'm on the wrong page
or I'm on the right page, but I'm on the wrong note.
And I've got to get in sync with everyone else to understand what's happening in this country.
I know some of y'all seen that before, but we got to see it over and over and over and over.
How are we going to get folks to hear? How?
We got to come from all sides, man.
We got to come from all angles.
Because guess what?
The repression of the revolution is already from all angles.
That's the Sia.
I got a whole song about it.
We have been under a psychological operation that has prevented us from even visualizing
and realizing revolution.
We got to get re-control of our minds.
How better to do that than through music?
Start there.
Get that rhythm to disrupt that rhythm.
Get a new melody.
Be theirs.
All them songs that we sung growing up about this goddamn country.
Never again.
I really was over there singing, and I'm proud to be an American where at least I know I'm free.
Unbelievable.
I'm not free.
We live in a nation that still has slavery in the Constitution.
Incarcerated folks is working for all kinds of companies when they're inside and can't get hired by those same companies when they get out.
It's time to investigate what you believe.
The revolution won't be televised.
It won't be streamed.
It's behind your eyes, y'all.
It wasn't until I realized that I had bought into so many of the lies that I truly began to wake up.
And now folks will be angry because you won't let them stay asleep silently.
Now I got 808s with it.
So the beat gon' hit ya.
The revolution will be live.
My new album, Truth Translator, is movement music.
Move with me.